I am searching for my missing sister.
Shiharu Nanase does not exist.
Why?
Why did she die?
- Tell me, please!
- Calm down!
According to our findings,
you never had a younger sister.
What?
She never existed in the first place.
Some people are just made to never exist.
What are you talking about?
Nanase.
You have been talking about
someone who doesn't exist.
That's impossible.
Shiharu and I were always together.
So you won't come join me in Tokyo.
You'll instead stay here,
with Shiharu?
That's impossible.
You'll instead stay here,
with Shiharu?
Impossible.
That's impossible!
What's up?
I had a terrible dream.
Tell me about it.
In my dream, I disappeared.
It was as if I never existed.
No one even remembered my name.
Don't worry.
I won't ever forget you.
[A sister who never existed]
[Conflicting memories and speculations]
[log.5]
You're free to go.
I spoke with Dr. Furukawa.
We agreed there were misunderstandings,
and she graciously took back her charges.
She will remain your primary psychiatrist.
As if I'd go see her again.
I have no daughter.
Then why the funeral?
It was to help end your delusions.
Quit pulling my leg.
I will say it again.
I have no daughter.
Impossible.
How could I believe that?
Haruka.
I know you had a complicated relationship
with your mother.
Even though you only had each other.
How is this relevant?
Your mother once told me
she'd never seen you earnestly smile before.
But after our remarriage,
you slowly began to change.
You believed you had a younger sister.
She brought a smile to your face.
And we couldn't deny you
your one source of happiness.
So...
For years...
And years...
I was merely living a dream?
You created your ideal "family"
in order to protect your own heart.
Your mother told me you always had
quite the active imagination.
Like that monster you saw
when you were younger.
Do you know what an "imaginary friend" is?
It's a being that exists in your own mind.
Although it's a phenomenon
often seen in children,
some adults will "grow"
with these imaginary friends.
When you first raised a fuss
about your sister disappearing in the flood,
I was relieved.
I assumed you were
growing out of your fantasies.
I thought you finally decided
to focus on reality.
No...
Dr. Furukawa also gave me her diagnosis.
She said you were trying to
redo your mother's funeral.
That you regret
how you handled her death.
[Dear Haruka]
Haruka?
I don't believe it.
Professor Ishimizaki also knew about Shiharu.
I told him to entertain your fantasies.
Shiharu's DNA matched those bones.
The Professor was leaving me a message.
Even if that were true,
only Ishimizaki would know
the answer to that riddle.
Ishimizaki, who is now also gone.
You have to move on, Haruka.
I want you to treasure yourself.
How are the investigations going?
Well enough, I'd say.
I see.
You do not doubt my son, do you?
We're looking into the case from all angles.
Let's leave Ishimizaki's case to the police.
Won't you come to my place?
I'd like to be alone.
I won't force you to attend therapy anymore.
Just please, continue to take your medicine.
Haruka.
I think of you like my real son.
If nothing else, trust me on this.
Hey there, Tada.
Got any new leads?
That was Kyoichi Nanase, right?
The head of Nichie Pharmaceutical.
Yeah. He just came to get his son.
- Tada.
- His son? Something happened to him?
- Mayuzumi, let's go.
- Hold on, Tada.
You remember Onodera, yeah?
Don't you wanna know what he was chasing
before he was killed?
You got something?
Tell me about Nanase's son.
I'm taking a smoke.
Nanase's son was ambushed?
Why?
Beats me.
How is Kyoichi Nanase's son
involved in this case?
He found Ishimizaki's body.
He worked in his lab, too.
The lab where the bones were stolen from?
The bones from... where was it...
Roopkund.
Nanase's son is at the center of this case.
Yeah, well, he was just looking for someone.
Who?
An imaginary sister.
We were all at the whims
of a delusional grad student.
Including the poor girl
who was roped into the search.
He had someone helping him?
Yeah, Ishimizaki's niece.
I don't know much about her, though.
Surely you know something.
That's enough from me for now.
Tell me what you know.
Fair enough.
And you'd better tell me everything.
It's all tied to the Plantae.
- Damn it...
- What?
They've got political connections,
and ties to our higher-ups.
You'd better not be bluffing.
They're a hard target for us.
I'm still looking into
the specifics of it all.
But I'm certain the Nichie President
and Plantae are connected somehow.
I've even got a photo to prove it.
Want to take a look?
Please leave your message after the tone.
Yui. The police told me Mari is safe.
Tell me what's going on.
Hello?
My name is Nanase.
I worked at Professor Ishimizaki's lab.
Is this the home of the Professor's brother?
Did you need something from my husband?
No. I wish to speak to Yui, if she is home.
Yes?
I apologize if I seem suspicious.
Yui and I met at the Professor's funeral.
That is not funny.
My daughter passed away
six years ago in an accident.
Please do not bother us again.
What?
[Haruka]
Shiharu...
We're heading out, Tada.
HQ won't share their intel with us, huh?
Then let's get the jump on them.
What?
We have one lead over HQ.
I saw the face of this "Ushio". No one else.
Come on.
Have Xin Ming Ah been assertive
about buying us out?
Not at the moment.
But we cannot let our guard down.
I will continue to erase
any remains of "log.0".
Are there any concerns regarding the Plantae?
I know they've been sending out Ushio.
- If your family...
- That is none of your concern.
My apologies, sir.
I appreciate you looking out for my son.
I'm sorry to make you juggle so much.
I'm just glad he is alive and well.
Indeed.
I think the experience was necessary
for him to grow up, sir.
I reckon the hydrangeas will bloom soon.
You know, I finally saw
Haruka smile yesterday.
We made the right choice.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Do I add all this sugar?
Add as much as you want. It's your birthday.
Then all in it goes.
Hey, look. Twins.
Woah, that's rare.
I wonder which one's the real chick.
Huh? They both are.
- Right.
- The yolks are right there.
Fair point.
Shiharu, should I really be whisking by hand?
It feels like I'll be whisking forever.
No.
Shiharu was here.
She was right here.
Her clothes.
Shiharu's...
Why?
Stop.
Stop it.
Stop!
I need to ask a favor.
You've been looking into
Kyoichi Nanase, I assume?
Yes.
And his family, too?
But of course.
I want information,
specifically about his son.
Do you have a lead?
That's what I want to know.
I bet it ties into all this somehow.
Fine. I'll gather our findings for you.
Where are you right now?
I'm about to infiltrate enemy territory.
Take care not to be eaten alive.
I am Kasuga, the head of PR
for the Plantae Gathering.
Excuse me.
I am Hirama, editor-in-chief of Toho Journal.
- Please, have a seat.
- Thank you.
I read through your draft.
Thank you.
Though your organization
is commonly seen as a religious one,
the Plantae Gathering is also a crucial NPO.
I hoped to make such things clear
with this article.
If that sounds alright with you?
So long as I get eyes on the final draft.
Of course.
"All who suffer must offer
their flesh and blood
to quench thy thirst."
"All sacrifice will one day
return to your body."
"Like Plantae, who bear fruit
and flourish in rain."
So are the teachings
of Brother Sojiro Manabe.
Such inspiring words.
I believe we said no photography allowed?
Right, my apologies. Habits are habits.
I feel a real sense of community here
that has been lost in our modern era.
Indeed.
We want our believers
to all help one another.
We do not promote fraudulent scams,
nor generous offerings of any sort.
Fascinating.
I am impressed with Mr. Manabe's network.
He knew people in politics, finance -
all over, really.
And you maintain various connections
even after his death?
Yes. We do frequent volunteer work
to engage with people
from many different fields.
I see.
[Sharing memories of "the Land of Souls"]
[Sojiro Manabe x Yumihiko Nanase]
Ms. Kasuga, a moment?
- May I?
- Of course.
Excuse me.
[Dear Shiharu]
Thank you for your time today.
Thank you for visiting.
This is a painting by Brother Sojiro Manabe
of a place he visited in India.
India?
"The Land of Souls".
It is said to be a sacred land.
I shall remain in touch.
Please do.
Thank you again for having me.
- Hello.
- Hey there.
Was your infiltration a success?
I blended right in.
Here is everything we have
on the Nanase family.
I sent you the digital files as well.
Thank you, thank you.
Let's see here...
So Haruka is his step-son.
This was Kyoichi's first marriage.
And Haruka's mother was named Kaede Tozaki.
Wait a second...
Is she really...
Yes. I'm sure of it.
We hadn't noticed the connection
until now either.
To acquire such intel so easily...
Wish I could boast to the police about it.
We aren't a charity case, understand?
Yeah, I hear you.
I found something tying this case
to Nichie, and the Plantae.
Bones?
It's a place in the Himalayas.
A lake, called Roopkund.
Those at Plantae call it "the Land of Souls".
Souls...
That being said, I still don't have enough
to reach Kyoichi Nanase.
The stolen remains from Roopkund, huh?
I can't find anything.
Sorry to scare you!
I'm Hirama, from Toho Journal.
I'm investigating the matters surrounding
Professor Ishimizaki's death.
You must be an acquaintance
of the Professor, yes?
Were you the individual
helping Haruka Nanase search for his sister?
I'd like to speak with you.
I promise, I'm on your side.
Please, if I could just have a moment.
I'd like to hear what you know.
You were ambushed by
a mysterious man, correct?
In looking into the disappearance
of Haruka's sister,
you got too close to the truth
of another mystery.
I received a warning from him as well,
back when I was none the wiser.
You too?
How much do you and Haruka know
of the Plantae Gathering?
Plantae?
Yes.
What are you talking about?
You don't know?
Is there a lead there?
Haruka didn't tell you about them?
We were looking into an individual
named Kayoko Senba.
The developmental biologist.
A biologist.
Then she knew Professor Ishimizaki?
They were both a part
of the same research team 27 years ago.
Were they doing research at Roopkund?
I knew something was up with that lake.
Haruka's father was a part
of the research team as well.
Kyoichi Nanase?
What happened at Roopkund? Please, tell me.
I'm still not certain.
But this I can say for sure.
You shouldn't get involved any further.
This case is a dangerous one.
Mrs. Senba told us the same thing.
I see.
That "Senba" gave you good advice.
Would it help to ask Nanase about all this?
Kyoichi Nanase, I mean.
Well, now.
You can't just book a meeting with him.
I have someone I'm looking for.
I've already lost a friend
who had gotten too involved in this case.
Remember, I'm with Toho Journal.
I promise to report a big scoop for you.
She exists.
Shiharu exists.
She'll come back.
[Dear Shiharu]
Shiharu exists.
Shiharu...
She exists.
I'm sorry, Shiharu.
What the...
[Giving birth to you, was my greatest gift.]
[Kaede]
Mom...
Mom gave birth to Shiharu?
Kei.
Want some ice cream?
- Really?
- Of course.
Yay!
You are my accomplice.
I wonder who could be visiting at this hour?
Hello?
Yes, she's home. May I get a name?
Yes, I'm safe.
Thank you for letting me escape.
Of course! It was fun for me, too.
But my mother-in-law
gave those poor officers hell.
It's like she has to look down on everyone.
So? Have you figured out
my mother-in-law's secret?
Not yet. I'll need a bit more time.
I see.
She's been on edge since you escaped,
so I thought something happened.
She usually keeps
her emotions in check, you know?
Maybe that's why
she's attached to my son these days.
It's seriously annoying.
Where is she now?
She's in her room entertaining a guest.
I can't believe anyone would visit so late.
Welcome home, Haruka Nanase.
I've been waiting for you.
I am Hirama, from Toho Journal.
It all began with the bones from Roopkund.
Isn't that right?
Everything began 27 years ago,
during a particular research expedition.
An expedition your step-father
also participated in.
This all ties back
to the previous Nichie head.
I think Nichie Pharmaceutical
funded that entire expedition.
And now, they're trying to cover it up.
Why come to me about this?
You're not so innocent, are you?
Professor Ishimizaki,
who was a part of the team,
and asked you to analyze
those Roopkund remains,
was murdered.
You yourself were assaulted
for looking into Kayoko Senba,
another member of the team.
What exactly is at Roopkund?
That's what I want to know.
You aren't fooling me.
What do you think I know?
Your mother passed away seven years ago, yes?
My guess is that her death
is tied to all this as well.
Those in Plantae call Roopkund,
"the Land of Souls".
They worship the place.
What's so special about that lake?
You'd know, wouldn't you?
As a former Plantae worshipper.
My mother was the religious one.
"All who suffer must offer
their flesh and blood
to quench thy thirst."
"All sacrifice will one day
return to your body."
"Like Plantae, who bear fruit
and flourish in rain."
Please leave.
"Like Plantae, who bear fruit
and flourish in rain."
"Rain does not choose the dry.
It supplies to all."
"Water climbs the heavens,
till it returns to Earth."
Forgive them.
Everything will be okay.
All manners occur in an eternal cycle.
Are the Plantae involved
in everything that's going on?
Yeah. I'm sure of it.
You really don't know anything?
Even though both founders have died,
the tie between Nichie and Plantae remains.
You should be close to the truth.
Isn't there anything you've realized?
Some secret they wouldn't mind
killing a man to keep.
Please.
Please set me free.
Roopkund, also known as the Land of Souls.
But to me?
It's become nothing more than a cursed lake.
Have you caught on to something?
Kayoko Senba is a developmental biologist.
And what of it?
No, I see now.
You were ambushed
for looking into Kayoko Senba.
She's at the center of it all.
Woah there.
You okay?
Excuse me. I'd like to see President Nanase.
Sir.
I have news regarding the funding of "log.0".
Change of plans. We'll talk later.
- But sir, the funds...
- Later.
Now leave me.
Yes, sir.
Then if you'll excuse me.
Welcome.
I am Ishimizaki's daughter, Mari.
I came to ask about Shiharu Nanase.